{
    "id": "5cac74e1ae0e42348dedb7d8eeb51e19",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The child ran ……………………….. the road.",
            "description": "To run across a road is to move from one side to the other side.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4377712b51ad44ef88a686b6147e412d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news from …………………………. the borders is quite disquieting.",
            "description": "Across and over can mean on or to the other side of a line, river, road etc.",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "across",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df6f9364b38549c781bd5f5d4873d5d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got up early ………………………….. the morning.",
            "description": "We use in with parts of the day.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "023a11b65d45463bb429a7de621c03b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She arrived ………………………….. Monday.",
            "description": "Before days we use on.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1da8dc3948524071b9faa7977c1b65e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can run 4 miles ……………………… a stretch.",
            "description": "At a stretch means in one continuous period.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc72e3f91af94c04a75fec4fb9778601"
        },
        {
            "question": "We usually go swimming ………………………… the weekend.",
            "description": "Either on or at can be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ab42d6ca4834bbcb5604480dbb2e83b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hall can seat ………………………… 700 people.",
            "description": "To talk about quantity we use up to.",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "until",
                "as much as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b92f8cb67bf24072965ae4b8cd253110"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting has been postponed ………………………… Friday.",
            "description": "Either till or until can be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9e4a74904cb479bb045c63fd9f5e48f"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a restaurant ………………………….. the road.",
            "description": "Sometimes both up and down can mean along.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "up",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b8e860c3a3e44fa3bf27c0f46c94adeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting must start …………………………….. time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4de764704af4f4fbd55d3e10c2cb7a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him …………………………. Monday.",
            "description": "Since is used with the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "721e9ce16aed420fb9727c27e3c82a70"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be here ……………………….. two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ad37f304acc48ccacd427ff385d6675"
        }
    ]
}